Run, don't walk to see Walk, Don't Run.
Walk Don't Run is a comedy, romance film directed by Charles Walters.
During the housing shortage of the Summer Olympic Games in 1964, two men and a woman share a small
apartment in Tokyo, and the older man soon starts playing Cupid to the younger pair.
Sir William Rutland, played by Cary Grant.
Christine Easton, played by Samantha Eggar.
Steve Davis, played by Jim Hutton.
Julius D. Haversack, played by John Standing.
Aiko Kurawa, played by Miiko Taka.
Yuri Andreyovitch, played by Ted Hartley.
Walk, Don't Run is a 1966 American romantic comedy film directed by Charles Walters (in his final film as a
director), and starring Cary Grant (in his final film role), Samantha Eggar, and Jim Hutton.
It follows a travelling industrialist visiting Tokyo, and accompanying a male
athlete and a female apartment tenant, during the 1964 Summer Olympics.
The film is a remake of the 1943 film The More the Merrier.
The title stems from the basic rule of racewalking: that competitors
must not run at any point (both feet leaving the ground).
The film explores themes of hotel room, olympic
games, embassy, housing shortage.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.